--Ep Title
Episode 57
Tokyo Colony No. 1, Part 4
--Bottom text
Hazenoki Iori, 35 Points
Reggie Star, 41 Points
Hari Chizuru, 28 Points
--Rule 10
Players shall be able to view the following information on other players:
name, points, number of rules added, and current colony.
Players may transfer a number of points of their choosing to another player.
Takaba Fumihiko, 0 Points
Curse
--Curse
--Kogane: Search Results
Search Results
Higuruma Hiromi
Points
Rules
Added
Current Colony: Tokyo No. 1
--Kogane: Search Results (zoom)
Curse
--Phone
Mobile Terrace
Receipt
Monday, November 12th
Domain Expansion: Chimera Shadow Garden Points
--Next Ep
Next Episode
Tokyo Colony No. 1, Part 5